ABDUSH SHOMAD BUKHORI

Full Stack Software Engineer

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/asbukhori

Portfolios: https://asbukhori.github.io

Domicile:

Surabaya, East Java (Indonesia)

Phone:

+6285731229262

Email:

xom.albukhori@gmail.com

Summary

Professional Software Engineer with over 4 years of experience in developing web and mobile applications with more than 30 successful projects delivered which scope including Hospitality, Healthcare, E-Commerce, Online Shop, Company Profile, Games, E-Vote, Personal Blog and Fintech. Think critically in solving problems effectively and efficiently.

Skill

- Web Service API (Advance)
- CodeIgniter 3 (Advance)
- Golang (Intermediate)
- ReactJS (Intermediate)
- Flutter (Intermediate)

- MySQL (Intermediate)
- PostgreSQL (Intermediate)
- Fast Learning
- Project Management

Experience

Acting Head of IT Department - Jun 2021 to Sept 2022

PT. Mamalyfe Selalu Diberkati, Contract

- Taking care in every concept/idea that will be applied to the application with 5-8 team members and the vendor (external team).
- Understand at least 90% of the overall system architecture (there are more than 7 repositories) applications in the first 4 months of work and master the stacks used.
- Coding and Testing both Backend (API, Third party Integration) and Frontend (Assist Team when needed)

IT Project Manager – Mar 2019 to Apr 2021

PT. Alfath Teknologi Kreatif, Full-Time

- Developed more than 30 project applications for internal or client.
- Lead the projects with 2-6 team members in the application development process.
- Accompany and also be an advisor in meetings with the clients and also in making cooperation agreements.
- Provide advice and direction from presales to after sales in every collaboration with clients which increases client satisfaction by 90%.
- Create a custom CMS to be used in working on client projects in the real estate sector thereby increasing work speed by up to 80%.
- Manage up to 5 hosting platforms used by the company.

IT Manager – Aug 2018 to Apr 2021

Kelola.net, Full-Time

- Develop systems to process hundreds of thousands of data as a full stack.
- Implements server-side processing in data retrieval which increases data retrieval speed by 80%.
- Participate in every step of the company's journey from the beginning to acquiring hundreds of application users and get funding approximately IDR 300,000,000 from PPBT (Technology-Based Start-up Company) 2019 held by the Ministry of Research, Technology and Higher Education Indonesia.
- Leading meetings with the technical team, business team and company stakeholders.
- Supervise and assist 7 team members in testing, reviewing and analyzing both applications, sales or business strategies.
- Do Online and Offline Training Sessions during presales which increase the user acquisition rate by 90%.

Software Developer - Oct 2017 to Jul 2018

Syariahrooms Hospitality, Full-Time

• Create information systems required by the company which reduce overbooking cases to below 5% every month.

Education

Universitas Islam Negeri Maulana Malik Ibrahim Malang, East Java, Indonesia Bachelor of Computer Science, **Informatic Engineering**

- Member of the Informatics Engineering Student Association for the period 2018-2019
- Website Developer Mentor Coordinator at the 2018 Summer Program held by the Department of Informatics
- Laboratory Assistant Department of Informatics Engineering 2016-2017 and 2017-2018
- Vice chairman of the Weboender community (Community of Web Programming by Department) for the period 2018-2019.

Languages

Bahasa Indonesia – main English – secondary